kissinsights.com 2014-10-09

# Privacy Policy | Qualaroo - Behavior Insight Surveys For Smarter A/B Testing

Effective: August 30, 2013

This Privacy Policy explains how information is collected, used and disclosed by Qualaroo with respect to the access and use of our website and our services. This Privacy Policy doesn’t apply to any third-party websites, services or applications that you may access through our services.

**Information We Collect**

**_Non-Personally-Identifying Information_**

Like most website operators, Qualaroo collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Qualaroo’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Qualaroo’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Qualaroo may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website or services.  Qualaroo also collects information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Qualaroo does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the circumstances described below.

**_Personally-Identifying Information_**

Certain visitors to Qualaroo’s websites choose to interact with Qualaroo in ways that require Qualaroo to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Qualaroo gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up to create surveys to provide their email address. Qualaroo collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Qualaroo. Qualaroo does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.  We do not knowingly collect personal information from children.  If we learn that we have collected personal information of a child under 13, we will take steps to delete such information from our files as soon as possible.

**Information Collected for Others**

Through our services our customers can collect information about how their end users use their websites, as well as how those websites are performing. Our customers determine the types of data and information that is sent to Qualaroo for collection and analysis. The collection of this data and information by our customers is subject to their own privacy policy. Because our customers have the sole discretion to determine what data and information is collected about or from its users, our Privacy Policy does not apply to any end user data that we may collect, obtain, or access in connection with operating our service on behalf of our customers. We ask that our customers abide by all applicable laws, rules and regulations, including laws relating to privacy and data collection and post an online privacy policy that provides users with clear notice of its practices regarding data collection, use, and disclosure, however, we have no control over our customers’ activities or the disclosures they make in their privacy policy.

We may analyze end user data and information in the aggregate for purposes of internal research and/or to determine overall trends or metrics concerning how users are engaging with websites, and may report such general trends publicly, without disclosing any specific end user data and information.

**Cookies**

Our service collects information about our customers website’s visitors using cookies.  A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Qualaroo also uses cookies to help Qualaroo identify and track visitors to the Qualaroo website, their usage of Qualaroo website, and their website access preferences. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies but you can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

**How We Share the Information We Collect With Others**

Qualaroo will not share personally-identifiable information about you to anyone, unless you instruct us to do so or if we notify you that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information. If you are a registered user of the Qualaroo website and have supplied your email address, Qualaroo may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Qualaroo and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users.

Qualaroo may disclose non-personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Qualaroo’s behalf or to provide services available at Qualaroo’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Qualaroo’s website and services, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Qualaroo discloses personally-identifying information only when (or if we believe we are) required to do so by law, or when Qualaroo believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Qualaroo, third parties or the public at large. Qualaroo may also transfer and/or provide information about you in connection with an acquisition, sale of company assets, or other situation where customer and user information would be transferred as one of Qualaroo’s business assets.

We will share the data and information we collect for our customers with that customer. We do not share any specific end user data or information with individuals or with other companies, other than with the specific customer whose website transmitted the data and information to us. We may share information about our customers and their end users in anonymous and/or aggregated form with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling, research, analysis and other similar purposes.

**How to Access Your Information**

If you have an account, you can access and modify the information you provided us through your account. If you would like to terminate your account, please send us a request and we will use reasonable efforts to honor your request as soon as possible. Once your account is deactivated, you will not be able to access our services or your information through your account. 

**Security Measures We Take To Protect Your Information**

Qualaroo employs administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access, however, despite these efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse.  In the event that your personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will promptly notify you if your personal information has been compromised, as required by applicable law.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Any information that is collected is subject to our Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. Qualaroo may modify and revise its Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes to this policy, we will notify you of such changes by posting them on our website and we will indicate when such changes will become effective. Qualaroo encourages you to check back regularly for any changes to our Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy becomes effective will constitute your acceptance of such change.
